Boyhood
is every man's purest
and most passionate time.
Our mission is to rekindle the fire of life.
Our guests
will return to the campus
and recall their boyhood.
In the campus,
they can release pressure
and compete with each other.
Keep young forever.
To be brave
in the burning youth.
What should the freshmen do
on the first day here?
The placement tests.
EP01 Nice to Meet You.
Hello.
What's this?
Let me see.
Where is the teacher?
Hey, nobody wanna talk to me?
That's embarrassing.
Quick movement, masculine pose.
Good morning, sir.
Sit down.
I'm used to sitting here in school.
There's no camera.
You're right.
Go back.
Hello, everyone.
Welcome to Mango TV.
It's the VIP program "Boyhood".
This is the Boy College.
I'm your head teacher, Mr. Qi.
The quiz on the blackboard
is your first test.
Nathan Scott Lee is good.
You're 30.
And James Lee...
I've never wondered that
we would have such an "elderly student"
with a body age of 50 in our school.
James Lee, you are a old man!
I'm the eldest man.
You are the elderly,
not only the eldest.
Now let me introduce
the tradition in our college.
In every activity
you will be examined and observed
by a mysterious group.
Who are them?
Welcome!
One two one.
Boy group, boy group.
We are the fire in the school.
Okay, let the members of Boy Group
make their self-introductions.
Hello, I'm Shi Kai from SKY.
Hello.
When you hear my flow,
don't let it go.
I'm Li Wenjie.
Hello, I'm Sun Yuwei.
I'm studying in the branch campus of Boy Group in Toronto.
Hello.
I entered the Peking University by good performance in football.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Shao Mingming.
He's an auditor.
Only here for this class.
It doesn't matter.
The Boy Group is ready.
Now here comes the second quiz.
Attention.
From now on,
the questions are related to the freshmen.
One point for every correct answer.
No point for every wrong one.
This question is about
the "first times" in your life.
Now the first video.
It was many years ago.
That's great!
Good for you
to find it.
I remember it was
17 years ago.
It reminds me of
my efforts at that time.
As you recall it,
can we invite you to
dance it here?
Dance it here?
Is it okay?
Come on.
The dance in 17 years ago.
Bravo.
I want him.
Whose video
is the next one?
Cool!
James Lee
The same hairdo.
Thank you.
Have you prepared a guitar?
Sorry we are out of stock.
He should have one program.
He can sing a song.
Can you sing a song?
James Lee, sing that one.
"The Lover".
Okay.
We sing together.
"The Lover".
One, two, three.
He's so handsome.
Well, whose video
is the next one?
It's hard to be exceeded.
Who's that?
Oh my God.
That's Kido.
That was the first time
I sang on the stage in the true sense.
My first show.
The hair style is very important.
Kido, do you remember
what Nathan Scott Lee did just now?
Just do it.
Come on.
Music.
Cool.
We can be deskmates.
I can be his deskmate.
The next question we are going to take
is related to your Weibo.
Question 2: Who among the four new classmates has the most Weibo posts about themselves?
In other words, who likes to post their photos the most?
Now let's show the board.
I choose myself, too.
Who is the correct answer?
It must be mine.
Probably Kido.
I think Kido is also possible.
I'm not sure.
Kido!
We made a very detailed statistics.
Among your nearly 100 Weibo posts,
Kido, you send 42% updates about yourself.
Well, you're so fond of taking selfies.
You love taking selfies more than I think.
No, it's actually like this.
I seldom take pictures myself.
But sometimes fans will ask me
to post photos.
And they will ask me to start working as soon as possible.
My selfies are basically to
meet their needs.
Work for love.
Right.
So I take these photos.
Actually, I seldom take pictures myself.
But we also find
a very magical phenomenon.
Other brothers' contents
are very distinctive.
who like to post about their pets
on social platforms.
James Lee
So cool.
Jerry
You have a dog, too.
Happy
How was the fifth photo taken?
Was that taken by Happy?
Yeah, I'm trying to create that effect.
Next, you can guess what Nathan Scott Lee posts
most often.
His daughter.
Lucky
Right?
To be honest,
Of course.
I rarely post something about my daughter.
Because I
hope she can have
a very free childhood.
So it shouldn't be about my daughter,
it should be related to my wife's work.
In fact, among the 100 recent posts,
74 of Nathan Scott Lee's Weibo posts
are related to Stephy.
There are only 12 posts about him.
So sweet.
Others are about themselves,
but he is about Stephy.
In the third question
just now,
congratulations to Kido and Nathan Scott Lee.
They get the right answer, and plus one point for them.
Congratulations!
Thank you.
The next round is the strength test.
The next round is a strength game.
The four brothers like doing body-building exercises.
We have also collected
some photos about your fitness.
Please have a look.
It's gone now.
Me too.
You win.
You still have this figure.
Kido
As the old saying goes,
the stability of the chassis
depends on the strength of the thighs.
The most classic thigh wrestling game
is waiting for you.
Now fight your thigh strength.
Touch it.
No, no, no.
You can touch it
to test the strength.
The attacker is inside and the defender is outside.
Within the specified time,
the attacker only needs to spread the defender's legs,
and he wins.
Get ready.
Come on!
There is no advantage in leg length at this time.
Long legs are not good for exerting strength.
Yes.
I'm a little regret.
Whoever wins will attack first.
The winner attacks first.
Yes.
Rock-Paper-Scissors.
Get ready.
Three, two, one, start!
Start!
I don't try hard.
Look at the expression. He's working hard.
He's pushing hard.
It's awesome.
Come on!
James, you're still holding on.
Five,
four,
three,
two,
one.
OK.
James Lee won.
It doesn't matter.
You won in Rock-Paper-Scissors.
Right.
Yes.
Is it more difficult to attack?
Choose the defender.
Start
Harder
I'm dying!
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
It proves that the insider
is not more vulnerable.
But I want to give it a try.
I want to be the insider.
You want to be the insider?
You want to prove not only
your strong strength,
but also our weakness, right?
Alright.
Up to now, James Lee is number one.
He has a right
to double your scores
for four of you.
The right is to challenge the representative
from the Boy Group.
If you successfully challenge them,
all of your scores will be doubled.
Come over here.
I was enrolled in Peking University through the football bonus.
Challenge him.
Come on!
Pick the defensive.
No stress.
You want to be outside or inside?
I want to be inside.
No.
I want to try!
If you want to try, I'll play it with you later.
Just be outside.
Let's decide by Rock-Paper-Scissors.
Okay. Let's do it.
Winner's outside?
Rock, paper, scissors!
Bro, here's the thing.
I didn't win twice when I was inside.
And I feel so embarrassed today.
Think about it.
Be prepared.
Three, two, one. Go!
Fighting! Fighting! Fighting!
Be careful!
James Lee
Come on!
Fighting!
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Time is up!
So marvelous!
James Lee. You not only won the competition,
but also safeguarded my dignity!
Double!
Thank you.
Congratulations! James Lee won in the challenge!
Scores are doubled! Congratulations!
It shows that our brothers are really marvelous.
Right?
Okay.
Next, after the strength placement test,
we'll start our fourth question:
I have, but you do not!
Four students present have all attended
"Call Me by Fire" sponsored by SATINE.
Our new students, please show us your five fingers.
Please name an especial experience
in "Call Me by Fire" in sequence.
If the other three brothers don't have such an experience,
each of them should bend one finger.
Whoever bends all five fingers will be sifted out.
Let's challenge now.
Cannon has helped me to fold my clothes.
No, Cannon hasn't.
Then bend one finger.
Oh. It works like that.
So strange!
I've told you how to do it.
Bend your fingers.
A good kill!
Alright. Nathan Scott Lee.
Among all brothers, I may be
the one who sleeps lastly.
What time?
After 3:00 am.
I once slept at five o'clock.
Every day,
I sleep later than 3:00 am.
Every morning, Andrew would help me to make my bed.
I
have touched the chest of Jerry Yan.
Pay me!
You're so terrible!
I touched Jerry's chest.
It's Kido's turn.
In the show,
I've challenged Chiu Man-Cheuk with martial arts.
Good for you. I like people like you.
My God!
It's not easy to see you here.
Up till now,
all content of our placement test
is finished.
But scores haven't been finalized.
What are these five boys sitting here for?
They will play a role in reversion.
Every member of the Boy Group
has a right to add two points for once.
Now, please close your eyes.
All members in the Boy Group
stand
behind the new student you select.
Alright. Our new students.
Open your eyes.
Thank you.
Okay. Four new students,
please come here by our side.
The new students have successfully passed the
placement test through their efforts.
Now, it's time to announce
your total scores.
Let's welcome number one, Nathan Scott Lee,
to get your red reward!
So big!
Put it on him.
You look like a bridegroom, bro!
The second one is our James Lee.
Please get your red reward that is not that big!
How about me?
You can get a mini red reward.
Good.
It's pretty, isn't it?
It seems…
It seems to be prettier.
Cool.
Okay.
The placement test for new students today is over!
The campus life of the new students
will start from now on.
A youth for one day is a youth all his life.
I hope the four students
can still keep a young mindset
after entering into the Boy School.
There will be more stories waiting for you.
Thank you all!
And thanks to our friends from the Boy Group!
Let's call it a day!
Kido: My boyhood
Kido: is an era to keep stepping out of
Kido: the comfort zone and challenging myself.
Nathan Scott Lee: My boyhood is now.
Nathan Scott Lee: I'm still the youngster I used to be.
James Lee: My boyhood is an era accompanied by music.
James Lee: I hope every youngster is creative.
James Lee: Wish you health.
James Lee: Be brave to pursue your dreams.
Welcome to
Boy School Singer Competition.
Welcome!
The challenge starts!
Copy mine. Copying is not banned.
You've already found my defect.
Wait! I won't look at it!
Spoof us!
Spoof them!
The final result!